Guide to the Yale School of Music Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1930-1983; Accession 1989-A-121
  - Vienna Reports -- Responses, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Vienna Thank You Notes, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Material on Russia from Mrs. A. Ludman, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Yale Golf Course, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Library - General, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Band: National Wind Ensemble Conference: Feb., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Band: European Tour, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Penderecki Concert - 3/2/77, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Bernstein/Rostropovich Benefit, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Philharmonia: Sibelius, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Philharmonia: Washington Kennedy Center - Oct., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Philharmonia: Pittsburgh - 4/29, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Philharmonia: Kennedy Center - 10/28, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - [Yale Quartet], 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Yale Quartet, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Yale Symphony, 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Norfolk, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Norfolk, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Alumni Day at Norfolk, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Alumni Day at Norfolk, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Norfolk, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - American Musicological Society Convention
    - Minneapolis, 1978 October 19-21 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Los Angeles. Host: UCLA, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Chicago, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Chapel Hill, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Toronto, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Santa Barbara, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Michigan, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Washington, D.C., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Berkeley, California, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - American Musicological Society General, 1955-1974 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - American Musicological Society / College Music Society
    - Annual Meeting - 11/4-197 Washington, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Philadelphia / American Musicological Society: Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Annual Meeting - Washington, 1976 November 4-7 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Yale Univ., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - October - Panel, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Annual Meeting - Panel, 1978 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Annual Meeting - Evanston, 1977 November 17-20 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Annual Meeting - Rochester, 1975 November 14-16 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Spring Board Meeting - New York, 1977 March 25-26 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1975 Sep 19-21 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Iowa City, 1975 February (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - International Musicological Society, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Internatiounale Gesellschaft fur Musikwissenschaft, 1956-1977 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - International Musicological Society, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - International. Musicological Society - 8th Congress, undated (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - National Association of Schools of Music
    - 1975 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1975 Jun 17-20 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Annual Meeting - Atlanta, 1976 November 20-23 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - National Association of Schools of Music, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Chicago, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Annual Meeting - Colorado Springs, 1978 November 17-21 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - National Association of Schools of Music, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Philadelphia, 1979 November 18-20 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Forum, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - National Association of Schools of Music - The First Forty Years, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Denver, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - National Association of Schools of Music, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Kansas City, June, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - New Orleans, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Boston, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Bylaws, Regulations, Recommendations, 1965-1971 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Graduate Bulletin Revision, 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Society for Ethnomusicology (SEM), 1958-1968 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Connecticut Music Teachers Association, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Music Programs outside of Yale, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - University of Missouri, 1972 October 29- November 3 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Self-survey and Questionnaires, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - National Association of Schools of Music: Self-survey and Examination, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - National Association of Schools of Music: Self-survey -- Report and Correspondence, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Budd Report on Yale's Finances, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Chicago Symphony, 1976 November 9 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Annual Report [[see Box 24]]
    - 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Annual Report Questionnaires [see Box 24], 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Tirro, Frank: "Melody and the Markoff Chain Model", undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Annual Report [[see Box 24]], 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Library: Annual Reports [[see Box 24]], 1953-1978 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Review Committee on the Arts - Reports, undated (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Schola Cantorum - Paris, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Yale College Accreditation - Arts Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Annual Report Questionnaires, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Association of Yale Alumni - Arts Committee Report, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Curriculum Proposal, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - National Association of Schools of Music - General Correspondence - Dated, 1964-1973 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Sanford Series - General, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Sanford: Invitations and Thank-yous, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Sanford, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Sanford, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Women Musicians Series - Sanford, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Sanford, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Sanford Thank-you Notes, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Sanford Series, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Violin: Faculty Search [see Box 24], 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Oboe: Faculty Search [see Box 24], 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Faculty Search: General [see Box 24], 1975-1975 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Faculty Meetings
    - 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes: PFN, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Faculty [Meetings], 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Faculty Projection [see Box 24], 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Faculty Roster [see Box 24], 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Official Records (Budget, enrollment etc.) [see Box 24], 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Expenses, 1957-1970 (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Miscellany of Possible Interest to PN, 1937-1970 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Official Records [see Box 24], 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Budget [see Box 24], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Budget [see Box 24], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Sprague Budget [see Box 24], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Budget Work Documents [see Box 24], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Budget [see Box 24], 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Endowment Portfolio, [1967]-1972 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Needs Proposal [see Box 24], 1972 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Budget [see Box 24], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Proposal for Fiscal Self-sufficiency, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Budget [see Box 24], 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Budget Data [see Box 24], 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - MMA Exams - Comments [see Box 24], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - DMA [see Box 24], 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - DMA Program [see Box 24], 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - DMA Candidates SEE BOX24, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Evian Festival - Financial, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Evian Press, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Evian Travel, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Evian Programming, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Evian Festival, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Evian Operations, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Davis, Jr., Sammy, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Fruchtman, Milton: Sistine Ceiling, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - London, George, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Treger, Lawrence Rouse Company, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - Varga, Balint Andras of Editio Musica Budapest, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 332)
  - Velimirovic, Milos University of Virginia, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 333)
  - Self-survey, Reports [see box 25], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - Music Cabinet 1977-Billie Brown, Chairman, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - Yale Music Cabinet, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 349)
  - Academic Gowns, [1958-1960] (Box 8, Folder 350)
  - Alpha Phi Omega, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 351)
  - Ascension Church Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 8, Folder 352)
  - Ascension Lutheran Church, 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 353)
  - Appointment Corresondence, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 354)
  - Bibliography -- PFN, undated (Box 8, Folder 355)
  - Binghamton Torch Club - PFN, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 356)
  - Correspondence: RE: Furniture for Dean's Office, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 357)
  - PFN Radio Broadcast, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 358)
  - PFN Recommendations, 1962-1969 (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - Job Recommendations, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 360)
  - Travel Plans, undated (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - PFN - Travel, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - PFN's Travel Expenses, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - PFN Travel, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 364)
  - Pulitzer Prize, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - Arizona State University -- Correspondence, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 366)
  - Arizona State University, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - Arizona State University -- Undergraduate Program, 1958-1971 (Box 8, Folder 368)
  - Gammage Auditorium, 1960-1967 (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - Teaching Schedules, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 370)
  - YSM Students [see box 25], 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 371)
  - Ensemble Assignments, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - Atlanta Alumni, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - Calendar, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 374)
  - Calendar, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 375)
  - [Calendar Committee], 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - Catalog, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 378)
  - Concerto Competition:, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - Concert Calendar Committee, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - CMP Television Letter, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - CMP, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - CMP, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - Contemporary Music Project, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - CMP, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 385)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee [see box 25], 1971 (Box 9, Folder 386)
  - Faculty Meetings [see box 25], 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 387)
  - Faculty Meetings [see box 25], 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 388)
  - Faculty Meetings [see box 25], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 389)
  - Faculty Meetings: PFN [see box 25], 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 390)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes [see box 25], 1950-1972 (Box 9, Folder 391)
  - Employment Carbons - Prior to 9/68 [see box 25], 1951-1966 (Box 9, Folder 392)
  - Report on Yale Forum, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 393)
  - Degree Requirement Proposal: Committee of Fourteen, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 394)
  - Committee of Fourteen - proceedings, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 395)
  - Student Committee - C/14 - general, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 396)
  - Alumni Surveys - YSM, 1943-1956 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - The "Dominguez" Report, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 398)
  - Advisement [see box 25], 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 399)
  - European Trip, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 400)
  - PFN Travel, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 401)
  - Dean Nelson's Travel Forms, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 402)
  - PFN Travel Forms, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 403)
  - Entertaining Expenses - PFN, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 404)
  - Dean's Travel, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 405)
  - Graduate Club Bills, 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 406)
  - Film Program, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 407)
  - MMA Information [see box 25], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - MMA Reappraisals [see box 25], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 409)
  - Mosaics, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - Student teaching, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 425)
  - Guards, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 448)
  - Student Payroll, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 449)
  - Orchestral Assistants, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 450)
  - Lott, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 462)
  - Staff, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 474)
  - Norfolk - Staff/Faculty, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 475)
  - Staff, 1956-1965 (Box 10, Folder 476)
  - Annual Reports 70-1971 report, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 477)
  - Crisis Documents - May, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 478)
  - Black Music Students Union, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 479)
  - Communications from President's Office, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 480)
  - Norfolk - Budget - Management, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 481)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes (Luther Noss - Dean), 1964-1970 (Box 10, Folder 482)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes (Luther Noss - Dean), 1954-1964 (Box 10, Folder 483)
  - Solicitation Strategy Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 485)
  - Sprague, Peter J. '61, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 541)
  - Sprague, Peter J. '61, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 606)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 616)
  - YSM Official Records (Budget, Enroll., etc), 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 617)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 618)
  - Enrollment, etc., 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 619)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 620)
  - Enrollment, etc., 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 621)
  - Budget (Payroll Information), 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 622)
  - Budget, Enrollment, etc., 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 623)
  - Budget, Enrollment, etc., 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 624)
  - Budget, Enrollment, etc., 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 625)
  - Budget, Enrollment, etc., 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 626)
  - Annual Report and Related Documents, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 627)
  - Budget and Related Documents, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 628)
  - Annual Report and Related Documents, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 629)
  - Budget and Related Documents, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 630)
  - Annual Report and Related Documents, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 631)
  - Budget and Related Documents, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 632)
  - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 633)
  - Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 634)
  - Annual Report, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 635)
  - School Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 636)
  - School Budget, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 637)
  - Annual Report, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 638)
  - School Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 639)
  - Annual Report, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 640)
  - School Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 641)
  - Annual Report, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 642)
  - Annual Reports - Department of Music, 1951-1963 (Box 11, Folder 643)
  - Concerts, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 644)
  - Concerts (Chamber Series and Faculty Series), 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 645)
  - Norfolk - Staff, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 646)
  - Norfolk - Staff, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 647)
  - Norfolk - Budget and Management, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 648)
  - Norfolk - Budget and Management, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 649)
  - Norfolk - Educational Planning Historical, etc., 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 650)
  - Norfolk - Faculty, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 651)
  - American Choral Institute, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 652)
  - Lists of Norfolk Students for YSM catalogue, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 653)
  - Concert Office Forms (Programs and Press releases), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 654)
  - Concerts, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 655)
  - Norfolk Annual Report, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 656)
  - Choral Institute - Faculty and Staff, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 657)
  - Lists-of Norfolk Community at YSSMA, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 658)
  - Faculty (Appointments, No Soaps), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 659)
  - Seminar, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 660)
  - Music Department Evaluation, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 661)
  - Norfolk - Seminar, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 662)
  - Norfolk - General, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 663)
  - Norfolk - General Information, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 664)
  - Norfolk, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 665)
  - American Choral Foundation, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 666)
  - Norfolk, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 667)
  - Report re: Art Program, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 668)
  - Norfolk, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 669)
  - Norfolk Auditions, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 670)
  - Norfolk: Student Recitals, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 671)
  - Student Responses to Norfolk Program (Questionnares), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 673)
  - Annual Reports: Art and Music, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 674)
  - Norfolk: Budget Current, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 675)
  - Norfolk: Old Budgets, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 676)
  - Norfolk: Publicity, Articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 677)
  - Norfolk: Rosters of Students, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 678)
  - Norfolk: Programs, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 680)
  - Director's Report of the Music Division of the Yale Summer School of Music and Art, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 681)
  - Norfolk: Programs, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 682)
  - Norfolk: Programs, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 683)
  - Art Division Report, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 684)
  - Art School Report and History, 1953-1970 (Box 13, Folder 685)
  - Norfolk: Programs, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 686)
  - Norfolk: Student Recital Programs, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 687)
  - Norfolk, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 688)
  - Report on Norfolk, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 690)
  - Art Report, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 691)
  - Art Division - Norfolk, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 692)
  - Art School, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 693)
  - Norfolk, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 694)
  - Norfolk Report, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 695)
  - Norfolk Report, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 696)
  - Norfolk
    - 1975 (Box 13, Folder 697)
    - 1974 (Box 13, Folder 698)
    - 1973 (Box 13, Folder 699)
    - 1972 (Box 13, Folder 700)
    - 1971 (Box 13, Folder 701)
    - 1970 (Box 13, Folder 702)
    - 1969 (Box 13, Folder 703)
    - 1968 (Box 13, Folder 704)
    - 1967 (Box 13, Folder 705)
    - 1966 (Box 13, Folder 706)
    - 1965 (Box 13, Folder 707)
    - 1964 (Box 13, Folder 708)
    - 1963 (Box 13, Folder 709)
    - 1962 (Box 13, Folder 710)
    - 1961 (Box 13, Folder 711)
    - 1960 (Box 13, Folder 712)
    - 1957 (Box 13, Folder 713)
    - Concerts, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 714)
    - Early Music Workshop, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 715)
    - Faculty and Staff, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 716)
    - Form Letters, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 717)
    - Students - Lists, Letters, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 718)
    - Transportation, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 719)
    - Wilanowski Kwartet (Wilanow) - Poland, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 720)
    - Kreuzberger Quartet, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 721)
    - Architects - H.S. Newnan, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 722)
    - Budget [see box 25], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 723)
    - Chamber Music Session, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 724)
    - Concerts, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 725)
    - Early Music Seminar, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 726)
    - Faculty and Staff [see box 25], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 727)
    - Kreuzberger Quartet, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 728)
    - Recitals and Programs, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 729)
    - Student Recitals, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 730)
    - Students -Lists, Letters, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 731)
    - Wilanow Quartet, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 733)
    - Report, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 734)
    - Budget [see box 25], 1973 (Box 13, Folder 735)
    - Budget and Finances [see box 25], 1974 (Box 13, Folder 736)
    - Lists, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 737)
    - Student Recitals, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 738)
    - Norfolk Concerts, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 739)
    - Budget - Guidelines, etc. [see box 25], 1975 (Box 13, Folder 740)
  - Concerts, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 741)
  - Yale Summer School of Music and Art - Report Upon Financial Statements [see box 25], 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 742)
  - Art School, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 743)
  - Student Recitals, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 744)
  - Opera, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 745)
  - Norfolk: Correspondences, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 746)
  - General, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 747)
  - Students, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 748)
  - May Correspondence, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 749)
  - April Chronological Filing, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 750)
  - Budget [see box 25], 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 751)
  - Operations Improvement Program for Office of Undergraduate Admissions of Yale University, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 752)
  - Comparison of Actual and Budgeted Income and Expenses Yale University, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 753)
  - Yale University Proposed Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 754)
  - Yale University Proposed Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 755)
  - Yale University Proposed Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 756)
  - Proposal for a Study of Office of Undergraduate Admissions of Yale University, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 757)
  - School of Kusic Financial Results, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 758)
  - Approved Budget: By Unit, By School, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 759)
  - July - Chronological Filing, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 760)
  - August - Chronological Filing, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 761)
  - June Correspondance, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 762)
  - Faculty Typing, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 763)
  - March Chronological Filing, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 764)
  - February - Chronological Filing, Correspondence Keith Wilson, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 765)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 766)
  - January - chronological Filing, (Keith Wilson), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 767)
  - December - Chronological Correspondence, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 768)
  - October - Chronological Filing, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 769)
  - November - Chronological Correspondance, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 770)
  - September - Chronological Filing, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 771)
  - Sumer Music Program at Norfolk, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 772)
  - General, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 773)
  - Applicants, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 775)
  - Recitals, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 776)
  - Correspondence - Brandford College, 1973-1977 (Box 14, Folder 778)
  - Chronological Files
    - April, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 781)
    - March, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 782)
    - February, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 783)
    - January, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 784)
    - December, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 785)
    - November, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 786)
    - October, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 787)
    - September, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 788)
    - August, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 789)
  - Broadus, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 790)
  - Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 791)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 792)
  - Finland, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 793)
  - General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 794)
  - M.E.C. (Music Executive committee), 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 795)
  - Performance Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 796)
  - Steering Committee [see box 25], 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 797)
  - Admissions Packets, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 799)
  - Yale - Admission Application, 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 800)
  - Admissions Material, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 801)
  - Friends of Muxic, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 803)
  - Music Magazines (Advertising), 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 804)
  - Yale - Early Advertisements, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 805)
  - Yale - Key Notes - One Column Advertisements, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 806)
  - Yale - Competitors- Ad. samples, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 807)
  - School of Art: Department of Design, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 808)
  - Yale - Musical Instrument Collection, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 809)
  - Composing on Film, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 810)
  - Subscription Offers, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 811)
  - Yale - News Releases, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 812)
  - Concert Office, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 813)
  - Yale - Publicity, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 814)
  - Recital Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 815)
  - Fruchtman Film, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 816)
  - Ellington Fellowship, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 817)
  - Yale - Fund Raising, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 818)
  - Campaign for Yale, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 819)
  - Divinity School, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 820)
  - Keyboard Brochure, undated (Box 15, Folder 821)